I'm always excited for you!
(Leonard:)I'm excited that you found
this new job
(Leonard:)where you're making
decent money.
(Penny:)Decent? I make twice
what you make.
Wait, twice?!
(Howard:)Yeah.
Like, "times two" twice?
(Wil:)For those of you at home,
Leonard just found out
his fiancée makes
way more money than he does.
(Wil:)Let's listen.
(Leonard:)I went to school
for half my life.
(Leonard:)I have a doctorate.
(Leonard:)I'm still paying off
college loans.
(Penny:)Well, how much do you owe?
(Penny:)Maybe I can help you out.
(Leonard:)Wil, can we just turn off
the podcast for a little bit?
(Wil:)For those of you at home,
I am shaking my head "no."
(Amy:)How's it going, Sheldon?
Wonderful!
(Sheldon:)I just finished
hanging the lights.
(Amy:)Can I come in?
(Sheldon:)Yes, oh,
but enter through the side.
(Sheldon:)Batman is
a load-bearing blanket.